
const cardData = [


  {
    "unit": "轻松学中文3 第一单元",
    "words": [
      { "question": "亲戚", "answer": ["relative"] },
      { "question": "爷爷", "answer": ["grandfather",'grandpa'] },
      { "question": "奶奶", "answer": ["grandmother",'grandma'] },
      { "question": "大伯", "answer": ["uncle"] },
      { "question": "叔叔", "answer": ["uncle"] },
      { "question": "姑姑", "answer": ["aunt"] },
      { "question": "外公", "answer": ["grandfather",'grandpa'] },
      { "question": "外婆", "answer": ["grandmother",'grandma'] },
      { "question": "舅舅", "answer": ["uncle"] },
      { "question": "阿姨", "answer": ["aunt"] },
      { "question": "姨妈", "answer": ["aunt"] },
      { "question": "孩子", "answer": ["child"] },
      { "question": "儿子", "answer": ["son"] },
      { "question": "女儿", "answer": ["daughter"] },
      { "question": "瓜子脸", "answer": ["oval face"] },
      { "question": "个子", "answer": ["height"] },
      { "question": "报纸", "answer": ["newspaper"] },
      { "question": "春节", "answer": ["Spring Festival"] },
      { "question": "圣诞节", "answer": ["Christmas"] },
      { "question": "漂亮", "answer": ["beautiful"] },
      { "question": "帅", "answer": ["handsome"] },
      { "question": "圆", "answer": ["round"] },
      { "question": "瘦", "answer": ["thin"] },
      { "question": "胖", "answer": ["fat"] },
      { "question": "直", "answer": ["straight"] },
      { "question": "着急", "answer": ["anxious"] },
      { "question": "流鼻涕", "answer": ["runny nose"] },
      { "question": "拉肚子", "answer": ["diarrhea"] },
      { "question": "去世", "answer": ["passed away"] },
      { "question": "见面", "answer": ["meet"] },
      { "question": "不见", "answer": ["disappear", "not meet"] },
      { "question": "帮", "answer": ["help"] },
      { "question": "找", "answer": ["find"] },
      { "question": "给", "answer": ["give"] },
      { "question": "量体温", "answer": ["measure body temperature"] },
      { "question": "开药", "answer": ["prescribe medicine"] },
      { "question": "踢足球", "answer": ["play soccer"] },
      { "question": "受伤", "answer": ["get injured"] },
      { "question": "请假", "answer": ["ask for leave"] },
      { "question": "每年", "answer": ["every year"] },
      { "question": "前年", "answer": ["the year before last"] },
      { "question": "...的时候", "answer": ["when"] },
      { "question": "洛杉矶", "answer": ["Los Angeles"] },
      { "question": "纽约", "answer": ["New York"] },
      { "question": "需要", "answer": ["need"] },
      { "question": "不能", "answer": ["cannot"] },
      { "question": "所以", "answer": ["therefore"] },
      { "question": "一些", "answer": ["some"] }
    ]
  },
  {
    "unit": "轻松学中文3 第二单元",
    "words": [
      { "question": "暖和", "answer": ["warm"] },
      { "question": "雾", "answer": ["fog"] },
      { "question": "雷雨", "answer": ["thunderstorm"] },
      { "question": "凉快", "answer": ["cool"] },
      { "question": "西装", "answer": ["suit"] },
      { "question": "套装", "answer": ["set outfit", "suit"] },
      { "question": "连衣裙", "answer": ["dress"] },
      { "question": "游泳衣", "answer": ["swimsuit"] },
      { "question": "领带", "answer": ["tie"] },
      { "question": "围巾", "answer": ["scarf"] },
      { "question": "帽子", "answer": ["hat"] },
      { "question": "手套", "answer": ["gloves"] },
      { "question": "凉鞋", "answer": ["sandals"] },
      { "question": "皮鞋", "answer": ["leather shoes"] },
      { "question": "高跟鞋", "answer": ["high heels"] },
      { "question": "袜子", "answer": ["socks"] },
      { "question": "耳环", "answer": ["earring"] },
      { "question": "项链", "answer": ["necklace"] },
      { "question": "滑冰", "answer": ["ice skating"] },
      { "question": "滑雪", "answer": ["skiing"] },
      { "question": "钓鱼", "answer": ["fishing"] },
      { "question": "打排球", "answer": ["play volleyball"] },
      { "question": "打乒乓球", "answer": ["play table tennis"] },
      { "question": "打羽毛球", "answer": ["play badminton"] },
      { "question": "亲爱", "answer": ["dear"] },
      { "question": "已经", "answer": ["already"] },
      { "question": "当然", "answer": ["of course"] },
      { "question": "合适", "answer": ["suitable"] },
      { "question": "祝", "answer": ["wish"] },
      { "question": "当", "answer": ["become", "work as"] },
      { "question": "试", "answer": ["try", "test"] },
      { "question": "出差", "answer": ["business trip"] },
      { "question": "戴", "answer": ["wear"] },
      { "question": "季节", "answer": ["season"] },
      { "question": "寒假", "answer": ["winter vacation",'winter break'] },
      { "question": "暑假", "answer": ["summer vacation",'summer break'] },
      { "question": "雨伞", "answer": ["umbrella"] },
      { "question": "经理", "answer": ["manager"] },
      { "question": "公司", "answer": ["company"] },
      { "question": "律师行", "answer": ["law firm"] },
      { "question": "太阳", "answer": ["sun"] },
      { "question": "太阳", "answer": ["sun"] },
      { "question": "如果", "answer": ["if"] },
      { "question": "因为", "answer": ["because"] },
      { "question": "件", "answer": ["measure word for clothes"] },
      { "question": "顶", "answer": ["measure word for hats"] },
      { "question": "副", "answer": ["measure word for earrings"] },
      { "question": "双", "answer": ["pair (shoes)"] },
      { "question": "加拿大", "answer": ["Canada"] },
      { "question": "千", "answer": ["thousand"] },
      { "question": "万", "answer": ["ten thousand"] }
    ]
},
{
  "unit": "轻松学中文3 第三单元",
  "words": [
    { "question": "科目", "answer": ["subject"] },
    { "question": "物理", "answer": ["physics"] },
    { "question": "生物", "answer": ["biology"] },
    { "question": "化学", "answer": ["chemistry"] },
    { "question": "地理", "answer": ["geography"] },
    { "question": "教学楼", "answer": ["teaching building"] },
    { "question": "图书馆", "answer": ["library"] },
    { "question": "礼堂", "answer": ["auditorium"] },
    { "question": "操场", "answer": ["playground"] },
    { "question": "体育馆", "answer": ["gymnasium"] },
    { "question": "篮球场", "answer": ["basketball court"] },
    { "question": "足球场", "answer": ["soccer field"] },
    { "question": "游泳池", "answer": ["swimming pool"] },
    { "question": "停车场", "answer": ["parking lot"] },
    { "question": "教室", "answer": ["classroom"] },
    { "question": "实验室", "answer": ["laboratory"] },
    { "question": "厕所", "answer": ["restroom",'bathroom'] },
    { "question": "校长", "answer": ["principal"] },
    { "question": "教师", "answer": ["teacher"] },
    { "question": "办公室", "answer": ["office"] },
    { "question": "文具店", "answer": ["stationery store"] },
    { "question": "三楼", "answer": ["third floor"] },
    { "question": "校医室", "answer": ["school clinic"] },
    { "question": "文具", "answer": ["stationery"] },
    { "question": "铅笔", "answer": ["pencil"] },
    { "question": "尺子", "answer": ["ruler"] },
    { "question": "橡皮", "answer": ["eraser"] },
    { "question": "卷笔刀", "answer": ["pencil sharpener"] },
    { "question": "练习本", "answer": ["exercise book"] },
    { "question": "日记本", "answer": ["diary"] },
    { "question": "文具盒", "answer": ["pencil case"] },
    { "question": "计算器", "answer": ["calculator"] },
    { "question": "卡片", "answer": ["card"] },
    { "question": "小说", "answer": ["novel"] },
    { "question": "课本", "answer": ["textbook"] },
    { "question": "功课", "answer": ["homework"] },
    { "question": "测验", "answer": ["quiz"] },
    { "question": "考试", "answer": ["exam"] },
    { "question": "同学", "answer": ["classmate"] },
    { "question": "学期", "answer": ["semester"] },
    { "question": "兴趣", "answer": ["interest"] },
    { "question": "觉得", "answer": ["feel"] },
    { "question": "写", "answer": ["write"] },
    { "question": "介绍", "answer": ["introduce"] },
    { "question": "忘记", "answer": ["forget"] },
    { "question": "借", "answer": ["borrow"] },
    { "question": "还", "answer": ["return"] },
    { "question": "进", "answer": ["enter"] },
    { "question": "看见", "answer": ["see"] },
    { "question": "教", "answer": ["teach"] },
    { "question": "左边", "answer": ["left side",'left'] },
    { "question": "右边", "answer": ["right side",'right'] },
    { "question": "中间", "answer": ["middle"] },
    { "question": "里面", "answer": ["inside"] },
    { "question": "旁边", "answer": ["beside"] },
    { "question": "隔壁", "answer": ["next door"] },
    { "question": "难", "answer": ["difficult"] },
    { "question": "容易", "answer": ["easy"] },
    { "question": "有用", "answer": ["useful"] },
    { "question": "有意思", "answer": ["interesting"] },
    { "question": "行", "answer": ["okay", "fine"] },
    { "question": "为什么", "answer": ["why"] }
  ]
},

{
  "unit": "轻松学中文3 第四单元",
  "words": [
    { "question": "猪肉", "answer": ["pork"] },
    { "question": "牛肉", "answer": ["beef"] },
    { "question": "鸡肉", "answer": ["chicken"] },
    { "question": "虾", "answer": ["shrimp"] },
    { "question": "鱼柳", "answer": ["fish fillet"] },
    { "question": "猪排", "answer": ["pork chop"] },
    { "question": "香肠", "answer": ["sausage"] },
    { "question": "龙虾", "answer": ["lobster"] },
    { "question": "三文鱼", "answer": ["salmon"] },
    { "question": "牛排", "answer": ["steak"] },
    { "question": "鸭", "answer": ["duck"] },
    { "question": "肉丝", "answer": ["shredded meat"] },
    { "question": "鸡翅", "answer": ["chicken wing"] },
    { "question": "鸭蛋", "answer": ["duck egg"] },
    { "question": "三明治", "answer": ["sandwich"] },
    { "question": "薯片", "answer": ["potato chips"] },
    { "question": "薯条", "answer": ["french fries"] },
    { "question": "炸鸡翅", "answer": ["fried chicken wing"] },
    { "question": "沙拉", "answer": ["salad"] },
    { "question": "奶酪", "answer": ["cheese"] },
    { "question": "面包", "answer": ["bread"] },
    { "question": "酸奶", "answer": ["yogurt"] },
    { "question": "谷类早餐", "answer": ["cereal"] },
    { "question": "寿司", "answer": ["sushi"] },
    { "question": "咖喱牛肉", "answer": ["curry beef"] },
    { "question": "牛奶", "answer": ["milk"] },
    { "question": "杂菜汤", "answer": ["vegetable soup"] },
    { "question": "烤鸭", "answer": ["roast duck"] },
    { "question": "豆腐", "answer": ["tofu"] },
    { "question": "青菜", "answer": ["green vegetables"] },
    { "question": "盒饭", "answer": ["boxed meal"] },
    { "question": "绿茶", "answer": ["green tea"] },
    { "question": "甜品", "answer": ["dessert"] },
    { "question": "零食", "answer": ["snack"] },
    { "question": "饼干", "answer": ["biscuit"] },
    { "question": "糖果", "answer": ["candy"] },
    { "question": "冰淇淋", "answer": ["ice cream"] },
    { "question": "巧克力", "answer": ["chocolate"] },
    { "question": "蛋糕", "answer": ["cake"] },
    { "question": "炸", "answer": ["fry"] },
    { "question": "煎", "answer": ["pan-fry"] },
    { "question": "烤", "answer": ["roast"] },
    { "question": "烧", "answer": ["grill"] },
    { "question": "蒸", "answer": ["steam"] },
    { "question": "红烧", "answer": ["braise in soy sauce"] },
    { "question": "酸", "answer": ["sour"] },
    { "question": "甜", "answer": ["sweet"] },
    { "question": "咸", "answer": ["salty"] },
    { "question": "新鲜", "answer": ["fresh"] },
    { "question": "便宜", "answer": ["cheap"] },
    { "question": "饱", "answer": ["full"] },
    { "question": "饿", "answer": ["hungry"] }
  ]
},
{
  "unit": "轻松学中文3 第五单元",
  "words": [
    { "question": "邮局", "answer": ["post office"] },
    { "question": "诊所", "answer": ["clinic"] },
    { "question": "银行", "answer": ["bank"] },
    { "question": "百货公司", "answer": ["department store"] },
    { "question": "市政大楼", "answer": ["municipal building"] },
    { "question": "教堂", "answer": ["church"] },
    { "question": "公园", "answer": ["park"] },
    { "question": "咖啡馆", "answer": ["coffee shop"] },
    { "question": "购物广场", "answer": ["shopping mall"] },
    { "question": "车站", "answer": ["station"] },
    { "question": "服装店", "answer": ["clothing store"] },
    { "question": "自行车", "answer": ["bicycle"] },
    { "question": "手提包", "answer": ["handbag"] },
    { "question": "服装", "answer": ["clothing"] },
    { "question": "钱包", "answer": ["wallet"] },
    { "question": "钥匙", "answer": ["key"] },
    { "question": "手机", "answer": ["mobile phone"] },
    { "question": "现金", "answer": ["cash"] },
    { "question": "身份证", "answer": ["ID card"] },
    { "question": "学生证", "answer": ["student ID"] },
    { "question": "借书证", "answer": ["library card"] },
    { "question": "市中心", "answer": ["city center"] },
    { "question": "庙", "answer": ["temple"] },
    { "question": "河", "answer": ["river"] },
    { "question": "桥", "answer": ["bridge"] },
    { "question": "警察", "answer": ["police"] },
    { "question": "邻居", "answer": ["neighbor"] },
    { "question": "姓名", "answer": ["name"] },
    { "question": "生活", "answer": ["life"] },
    { "question": "办法", "answer": ["method"] },
    { "question": "声", "answer": ["sound"] },
    { "question": "看到", "answer": ["see"] },
    { "question": "骑", "answer": ["ride"] },
    { "question": "偷", "answer": ["steal"] },
    { "question": "留", "answer": ["stay"] },
    { "question": "搬家", "answer": ["move (house)"] },
    { "question": "听见", "answer": ["hear"] },
    { "question": "哭", "answer": ["cry"] },
    { "question": "叫", "answer": ["call", "shout"] },
    { "question": "醒", "answer": ["wake up"] },
    { "question": "注意", "answer": ["pay attention"] },
    { "question": "扔", "answer": ["throw"] },
    { "question": "转", "answer": ["turn"] },
    { "question": "过", "answer": ["pass"] },
    { "question": "方便", "answer": ["convenient"] },
    { "question": "烦人", "answer": ["annoying"] },
    { "question": "响", "answer": ["loud"] }
  ]
},
{
  "unit": "中文2 第1课",
  "words": [
    { "question": "读儿歌", "answer": ["read children's songs"] },
    { "question": "读书", "answer": ["read books"] },
    { "question": "读一读", "answer": ["read aloud"] },
    { "question": "画一画", "answer": ["draw a little"] },
    { "question": "画太阳", "answer": ["draw the sun"] },
    { "question": "画小马", "answer": ["draw a pony"] },
    { "question": "画红花", "answer": ["draw a red flower"] },
    { "question": "山水画儿", "answer": ["landscape painting"] },
    { "question": "年画儿", "answer": ["New Year painting"] },
    { "question": "喜欢写字", "answer": ["like writing characters"] },
    { "question": "喜欢说汉语", "answer": ["like speaking Chinese"] },
    { "question": "喜欢去学校", "answer": ["like going to school"] },
    { "question": "在家", "answer": ["at home"] },
    { "question": "在学校", "answer": ["at school"] },
    { "question": "在花园", "answer": ["in the garden"] },
    { "question": "教汉语", "answer": ["teach Chinese"] },
    { "question": "教汉字", "answer": ["teach Chinese characters"] },
    { "question": "写字", "answer": ["write characters"] },
    { "question": "写一写", "answer": ["write a bit"] },
    { "question": "写汉字", "answer": ["write Chinese characters"] },
    { "question": "说汉语", "answer": ["speak Chinese"] }
  ]
},

{
  "unit": "中文2 第2课",
  "words": [
    { "question": "教室里", "answer": ["in the classroom"] },
    { "question": "家里", "answer": ["at home"] },
    { "question": "学校里", "answer": ["in the school"] },
    { "question": "花园里", "answer": ["in the garden"] },
    { "question": "山里", "answer": ["in the mountain"] },
    { "question": "水里", "answer": ["in the water"] },
    { "question": "风里", "answer": ["in the wind"] },
    { "question": "雨里", "answer": ["in the rain"] },
    { "question": "云里", "answer": ["in the clouds"] },
    { "question": "中文书", "answer": ["Chinese book"] },
    { "question": "不来", "answer": ["not coming"] },
    { "question": "不好", "answer": ["not good"] },
    { "question": "不喜欢", "answer": ["not like"] },
    { "question": "那个同学", "answer": ["that classmate"] },
    { "question": "那本书", "answer": ["that book"] },
    { "question": "红笔", "answer": ["red pen"] },
    { "question": "黑笔", "answer": ["black pen"] },
    { "question": "我的笔", "answer": ["my pen"] },
    { "question": "他的笔", "answer": ["his pen"] },
    { "question": "本子", "answer": ["notebook"] },
    { "question": "书本", "answer": ["book"] },
    { "question": "一本书", "answer": ["a book"] },
    { "question": "讲一讲", "answer": ["talk a bit"] },
    { "question": "讲中文", "answer": ["speak Chinese"] },
    { "question": "讲汉语", "answer": ["speak Mandarin"] }
  ]
},

{
  "unit": "中文2 第3课",
  "words": [
    { "question": "放学", "answer": ["finish school"] },
    { "question": "今天", "answer": ["today"] },
    { "question": "今年", "answer": ["this year"] },
    { "question": "星期", "answer": ["week"] },
    { "question": "星期日", "answer": ["Sunday"] },
    { "question": "星期天", "answer": ["Sunday"] },
    { "question": "星期一", "answer": ["Monday"] },
    { "question": "星期二", "answer": ["Tuesday"] },
    { "question": "星期三", "answer": ["Wednesday"] },
    { "question": "星期四", "answer": ["Thursday"] },
    { "question": "星期五", "answer": ["Friday"] },
    { "question": "星期六", "answer": ["Saturday"] },
    { "question": "告诉", "answer": ["tell"] },
    { "question": "上午", "answer": ["morning"] },
    { "question": "中午", "answer": ["noon"] },
    { "question": "下午", "answer": ["afternoon"] },
    { "question": "朋友", "answer": ["friend"] },
    { "question": "小朋友", "answer": ["little friend", "child"] },
    { "question": "好朋友", "answer": ["good friend"] },
    { "question": "新朋友", "answer": ["new friend"] },
    { "question": "老朋友", "answer": ["old friend"] },
    { "question": "问一问", "answer": ["ask a bit"] },
    { "question": "问方向", "answer": ["ask for directions"] },
    { "question": "问老师", "answer": ["ask the teacher"] },
    { "question": "谁的书", "answer": ["whose book"] },
    { "question": "谁的车", "answer": ["whose car"] },
    { "question": "谁的本子", "answer": ["whose notebook"] },
    { "question": "谁的笔", "answer": ["whose pen"] },
    { "question": "听说", "answer": ["hear"] },
    { "question": "听写", "answer": ["dictation"] },
    { "question": "听一听", "answer": ["listen a bit"] },
    { "question": "听歌", "answer": ["listen to songs"] },
    { "question": "开心", "answer": ["happy"] },
    { "question": "放心", "answer": ["rest assured"] },
    { "question": "心里", "answer": ["in the heart"] },
    { "question": "好心", "answer": ["kind-hearted"] },
    { "question": "爱心", "answer": ["love", "compassion"] }
  ]
},
{
  "unit": "中文2 第4课",
  "words": [
    { "question": "用笔", "answer": ["use a pen"] },
    { "question": "用本子", "answer": ["use a notebook"] },
    { "question": "用心", "answer": ["attentively"] },
    { "question": "记下来", "answer": ["write down"] },
    { "question": "记一记", "answer": ["remember a bit"] },
    { "question": "日记", "answer": ["diary"] },
    { "question": "笔记本", "answer": ["notebook"] },
    { "question": "请坐", "answer": ["please sit"] },
    { "question": "请问", "answer": ["may I ask"] },
    { "question": "请上车", "answer": ["please get in the car"] },
    { "question": "请说中文", "answer": ["please speak Chinese"] },
    { "question": "谢谢", "answer": ["thank you"] },
    { "question": "谢谢爸爸", "answer": ["thank you, dad"] },
    { "question": "谢谢妈妈", "answer": ["thank you, mom"] },
    { "question": "谢谢老师", "answer": ["thank you, teacher"] },
    { "question": "对不起", "answer": ["sorry"] },
    { "question": "没关系", "answer": ["it doesn't matter"] },
    { "question": "没有", "answer": ["do not have"] },
    { "question": "没去", "answer": ["did not go"] },
    { "question": "没说", "answer": ["did not say"] },
    { "question": "没教", "answer": ["did not teach"] },
    { "question": "没看", "answer": ["did not see"] },
    { "question": "没做", "answer": ["did not do"] },
    { "question": "再见", "answer": ["goodbye"] },
    { "question": "再来", "answer": ["come again"] },
    { "question": "再去", "answer": ["go again"] },
    { "question": "做朋友", "answer": ["make friends"] },
    { "question": "做老师", "answer": ["be a teacher"] },
    { "question": "做学生", "answer": ["be a student"] },
    { "question": "做好孩子", "answer": ["be a good child"] },
    { "question": "孩子", "answer": ["child"] },
    { "question": "小孩子", "answer": ["little child"] },
    { "question": "好孩子", "answer": ["good child"] }
  ]
},{
  "unit": "中文2 第5课",
  "words": [
    { "question": "买面包", "answer": ["buy bread"] },
    { "question": "买水果", "answer": ["buy fruit"] },
    { "question": "买牛奶", "answer": ["buy milk"] },
    { "question": "买书", "answer": ["buy books"] },
    { "question": "买笔", "answer": ["buy pens"] },
    { "question": "买本子", "answer": ["buy notebooks"] },
    { "question": "买玩具", "answer": ["buy toys"] },
    { "question": "五岁", "answer": ["five years old"] },
    { "question": "六岁", "answer": ["six years old"] },
    { "question": "前天", "answer": ["the day before yesterday"] },
    { "question": "昨天", "answer": ["yesterday"] },
    { "question": "今天", "answer": ["today"] },
    { "question": "后天", "answer": ["the day after tomorrow"] },
    { "question": "给我", "answer": ["give me"] },
    { "question": "给老师", "answer": ["give to the teacher"] },
    { "question": "给奶奶", "answer": ["give to grandma"] },
    { "question": "书包", "answer": ["school bag"] },
    { "question": "面包", "answer": ["bread"] },
    { "question": "包子", "answer": ["steamed bun"] },
    { "question": "水果", "answer": ["fruit"] },
    { "question": "玩具", "answer": ["toy"] },
    { "question": "玩儿一玩儿", "answer": ["play a bit"] },
    { "question": "文具", "answer": ["stationery"] },
    { "question": "哥哥", "answer": ["older brother"] },
    { "question": "姐姐", "answer": ["older sister"] },
    { "question": "一张生日卡", "answer": ["a birthday card"] },
    { "question": "唱歌", "answer": ["sing a song"] },
    { "question": "唱一唱", "answer": ["sing a bit"] },
    { "question": "唱中文歌", "answer": ["sing Chinese songs"] }
  ]
},
{
  "unit": "中文2 第6课",
  "words": [
    { "question": "会不会", "answer": ["can you do"] },
    { "question": "不会", "answer": ["cannot"] },
    { "question": "会说", "answer": ["can speak"] },
    { "question": "会做", "answer": ["can do"] },
    { "question": "做事", "answer": ["do things"] },
    { "question": "高兴的事", "answer": ["happy things"] },
    { "question": "大事", "answer": ["big matter"] },
    { "question": "小事", "answer": ["small matter"] },
    { "question": "有事", "answer": ["have something to do"] },
    { "question": "没事", "answer": ["nothing to do"] },
    { "question": "别人", "answer": ["other people"] },
    { "question": "别说", "answer": ["do not say"] },
    { "question": "别走", "answer": ["do not leave"] },
    { "question": "别做", "answer": ["do not do"] },
    { "question": "别去", "answer": ["do not go"] },
    { "question": "别写", "answer": ["do not write"] },
    { "question": "别用", "answer": ["do not use"] },
    { "question": "收拾", "answer": ["tidy up"] },
    { "question": "收拾房间", "answer": ["tidy up the room"] },
    { "question": "收好", "answer": ["put away properly"] },
    { "question": "收起来", "answer": ["put away"] },
    { "question": "房间", "answer": ["room"] },
    { "question": "一个房间", "answer": ["a room"] },
    { "question": "房子", "answer": ["house"] },
    { "question": "书房", "answer": ["study room"] },
    { "question": "洗手", "answer": ["wash hands"] },
    { "question": "洗头", "answer": ["wash hair"] },
    { "question": "洗水果", "answer": ["wash fruit"] },
    { "question": "很饿", "answer": ["very hungry"] },
    { "question": "不饿", "answer": ["not hungry"] },
    { "question": "饿不饿", "answer": ["hungry or not"] }
  ]
},
{
  "unit": "中文2 第7课",
  "words": [
    { "question": "两个", "answer": ["two (things)"] },
    { "question": "两本", "answer": ["two books"] },
    { "question": "两人", "answer": ["two people"] },
    { "question": "一件事", "answer": ["one thing"] },
    { "question": "两件事", "answer": ["two things"] },
    { "question": "双手", "answer": ["both hands"] },
    { "question": "双脚", "answer": ["both feet"] },
    { "question": "双眼", "answer": ["both eyes"] },
    { "question": "双耳", "answer": ["both ears"] },
    { "question": "大脑", "answer": ["brain"] },
    { "question": "脑子", "answer": ["brain"] },
    { "question": "用脑", "answer": ["use one's brain"] },
    { "question": "工人", "answer": ["worker"] },
    { "question": "工作", "answer": ["work"] },
    { "question": "思考", "answer": ["think"] },
    { "question": "考一考", "answer": ["test a bit"] },
    { "question": "一万", "answer": ["ten thousand"] },
    { "question": "万一", "answer": ["just in case"] },
    { "question": "又写又画", "answer": ["write and draw"] },
    { "question": "又听又说", "answer": ["listen and speak"] },
    { "question": "做得好", "answer": ["do well"] },
    { "question": "唱不好", "answer": ["cannot sing well"] },
    { "question": "来得早", "answer": ["arrive early"] },
    { "question": "走不快", "answer": ["cannot walk fast"] },
    { "question": "看得见", "answer": ["can see"] },
    { "question": "看不见", "answer": ["cannot see"] }
  ]
},
{
  "unit": "中文2 第8课",
  "words": [
    { "question": "月亮", "answer": ["moon"] },
    { "question": "天亮了", "answer": ["it is dawn"] },
    { "question": "跟我去", "answer": ["follow me"] },
    { "question": "跟你们走", "answer": ["go with you"] },
    { "question": "为什么", "answer": ["why"] },
    { "question": "做什么", "answer": ["do what"] },
    { "question": "写什么", "answer": ["write what"] },
    { "question": "说什么", "answer": ["say what"] },
    { "question": "很大", "answer": ["very big"] },
    { "question": "很小", "answer": ["very small"] },
    { "question": "很多", "answer": ["very many"] },
    { "question": "很少", "answer": ["very few"] },
    { "question": "很好", "answer": ["very good"] },
    { "question": "很远", "answer": ["very far"] },
    { "question": "远方", "answer": ["distant place"] },
    { "question": "哪儿", "answer": ["where"] },
    { "question": "哪里", "answer": ["where"] },
    { "question": "哪个", "answer": ["which one"] },
    { "question": "哪件", "answer": ["which item"] },
    { "question": "觉得", "answer": ["feel"] },
    { "question": "高兴地说", "answer": ["happily said"] },
    { "question": "明白", "answer": ["understand"] },
    { "question": "明天", "answer": ["tomorrow"] },
    { "question": "明年", "answer": ["next year"] }
  ]
},
{
  "unit": "中文2 第9课",
  "words": [
    { "question": "时间", "answer": ["time"] },
    { "question": "小时", "answer": ["hour"] },
    { "question": "两个小时", "answer": ["two hours"] },
    { "question": "七个小时", "answer": ["seven hours"] },
    { "question": "黑夜", "answer": ["night"] },
    { "question": "夜里", "answer": ["at night"] },
    { "question": "夜间", "answer": ["nighttime"] },
    { "question": "光明", "answer": ["light", "brightness"] },
    { "question": "光亮", "answer": ["bright"] },
    { "question": "月光", "answer": ["moonlight"] },
    { "question": "阳光", "answer": ["sunlight"] },
    { "question": "星光", "answer": ["starlight"] },
    { "question": "亮光", "answer": ["light"] },
    { "question": "时光", "answer": ["time"] },
    { "question": "小河", "answer": ["small river"] },
    { "question": "河水", "answer": ["river water"] },
    { "question": "河流", "answer": ["river"] },
    { "question": "流水", "answer": ["flowing water"] },
    { "question": "流下来", "answer": ["flow down"] },
    { "question": "流星", "answer": ["shooting star"] },
    { "question": "流动", "answer": ["flow", "move"] },
    { "question": "走动", "answer": ["move around"] },
    { "question": "动作", "answer": ["action"] },
    { "question": "电动玩具", "answer": ["electric toy"] },
    { "question": "动画", "answer": ["animation"] },
    { "question": "动脑", "answer": ["use one's brain"] },
    { "question": "动手", "answer": ["use one's hands"] },
    { "question": "动笔", "answer": ["start writing"] },
    { "question": "湖水", "answer": ["lake water"] },
    { "question": "湖面", "answer": ["lake surface"] },
    { "question": "飞来飞去", "answer": ["fly back and forth"] },
    { "question": "飞得高", "answer": ["fly high"] },
    { "question": "飞得远", "answer": ["fly far"] },
    { "question": "飞上天", "answer": ["fly up to the sky"] },
    { "question": "飞下来", "answer": ["fly down"] },
    { "question": "游来游去", "answer": ["swim back and forth"] },
    { "question": "长大", "answer": ["grow up"] },
    { "question": "长高", "answer": ["grow taller"] },
    { "question": "想家", "answer": ["miss home"] },
    { "question": "想爸爸和妈妈", "answer": ["miss dad and mom"] },
    { "question": "想爷爷和奶奶", "answer": ["miss grandpa and grandma"] }
  ]
},
{
  "unit": "中文2 第10课",
  "words": [
    { "question": "种子", "answer": ["seed"] },
    { "question": "种花", "answer": ["plant flowers"] },
    { "question": "种瓜", "answer": ["plant melons"] },
    { "question": "种草", "answer": ["plant grass"] },
    { "question": "种树", "answer": ["plant trees"] },
    { "question": "来吧", "answer": ["come"] },
    { "question": "去吧", "answer": ["go"] },
    { "question": "吃吧", "answer": ["eat"] },
    { "question": "走吧", "answer": ["walk"] },
    { "question": "要种花", "answer": ["want to plant flowers"] },
    { "question": "要去公园", "answer": ["want to go to the park"] },
    { "question": "要买玩具", "answer": ["want to buy toys"] },
    { "question": "要看书", "answer": ["want to read books"] },
    { "question": "出发", "answer": ["depart"] },
    { "question": "发火", "answer": ["get angry"] },
    { "question": "发芽", "answer": ["sprout"] },
    { "question": "禾苗", "answer": ["seedling"] },
    { "question": "树苗", "answer": ["sapling"] },
    { "question": "小树", "answer": ["small tree"] },
    { "question": "树木", "answer": ["trees"] },
    { "question": "西瓜", "answer": ["watermelon"] },
    { "question": "冬瓜", "answer": ["winter melon"] },
    { "question": "南瓜", "answer": ["pumpkin"] },
    { "question": "黄瓜", "answer": ["cucumber"] },
    { "question": "果树", "answer": ["fruit tree"] },
    { "question": "果园", "answer": ["orchard"] },
    { "question": "水果", "answer": ["fruit"] },
    { "question": "小朋友一天一天长大了。", "answer": ["The little child grows bigger day by day."] },
    { "question": "小树一天一天长高了。", "answer": ["The small tree grows taller day by day."] }
  ]
},
{
  "unit": "中文2 第11课",
  "words": [
    { "question": "长江", "answer": ["Yangtze River"] },
    { "question": "江水", "answer": ["river water"] },
    { "question": "江河", "answer": ["rivers"] },
    { "question": "黄河", "answer": ["Yellow River"] },
    { "question": "古老", "answer": ["ancient"] },
    { "question": "中国", "answer": ["China"] },
    { "question": "外国", "answer": ["foreign country"] },
    { "question": "国家", "answer": ["country"] },
    { "question": "一条江", "answer": ["a river"] },
    { "question": "两条鱼", "answer": ["two fish"] },
    { "question": "它们", "answer": ["they (for animals or things)"] },
    { "question": "有名", "answer": ["famous"] },
    { "question": "名字", "answer": ["name"] },
    { "question": "他叫什么名字？", "answer": ["What is his name?"] },
    { "question": "最长", "answer": ["longest"] },
    { "question": "最多", "answer": ["most"] },
    { "question": "最少", "answer": ["least"] },
    { "question": "最大", "answer": ["biggest"] },
    { "question": "最小", "answer": ["smallest"] },
    { "question": "最远", "answer": ["farthest"] },
    { "question": "最高兴", "answer": ["happiest"] },
    { "question": "最热闹", "answer": ["busiest", "most lively"] },
    { "question": "最好看", "answer": ["most beautiful"] },
    { "question": "母亲", "answer": ["mother"] },
    { "question": "父亲", "answer": ["father"] },
    { "question": "双亲", "answer": ["parents"] },
    { "question": "亲人", "answer": ["relative"] },
    { "question": "从西流到东", "answer": ["flow from west to east"] },
    { "question": "从北流到南", "answer": ["flow from north to south"] },
    { "question": "从左写到右", "answer": ["write from left to right"] },
    { "question": "从上看到下", "answer": ["look from top to bottom"] },
    { "question": "从东走到西", "answer": ["walk from east to west"] },
    { "question": "从南飞到北", "answer": ["fly from south to north"] },
    { "question": "写着字", "answer": ["writing characters"] },
    { "question": "唱着歌", "answer": ["singing songs"] },
    { "question": "看着书", "answer": ["reading books"] },
    { "question": "中华", "answer": ["Chinese nation"] },
    { "question": "华夏", "answer": ["Huaxia (ancient name for China)"] },
    { "question": "华人", "answer": ["Chinese people"] }
  ]
},
{
  "unit": "中文2 第12课",
  "words": [
    { "question": "假日", "answer": ["holiday"] },
    { "question": "放假", "answer": ["have a holiday"] },
    { "question": "请假", "answer": ["ask for leave"] },
    { "question": "以后", "answer": ["after"] },
    { "question": "以前", "answer": ["before"] },
    { "question": "可以", "answer": ["can", "may"] },
    { "question": "旅游", "answer": ["travel"] },
    { "question": "动物", "answer": ["animal"] },
    { "question": "动物园", "answer": ["zoo"] },
    { "question": "海水", "answer": ["seawater"] },
    { "question": "海洋", "answer": ["ocean"] },
    { "question": "公园", "answer": ["park"] },
    { "question": "泳衣", "answer": ["swimsuit"] },
    { "question": "泳帽", "answer": ["swim cap"] },
    { "question": "游泳", "answer": ["swimming"] },
    { "question": "一点儿", "answer": ["a little bit"] },
    { "question": "家务活儿", "answer": ["household chores"] },
    { "question": "帮妈妈收拾房间", "answer": ["help mom tidy up the room"] },
    { "question": "生活", "answer": ["life"] },
    { "question": "快点儿", "answer": ["hurry up"] },
    { "question": "快乐", "answer": ["happy"] },
    { "question": "生日快乐", "answer": ["happy birthday"] },
    { "question": "假期快乐", "answer": ["happy holiday"] }
  ]
},



  
  
  ];
  

export default cardData;